{	"div":
	[	
		{
			"Problem":"364/4",
			"answer":"364/4",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"945/7",
			"answer":"945/7",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},
		
		{
			"Problem":"927/9",
			"answer":"927/9",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"595/7",
			"answer":"595/7",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"315/7",
			"answer":"315/7",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"550/5",
			"answer":"550/5",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"936/8",
			"answer":"936/8",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"828/9",
			"answer":"828/9",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},
		
		{
			"Problem":"597/3",
			"answer":"597/3",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"148/4",
			"answer":"148/4",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"848/8",
			"answer":"848/8",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"790/2",
			"answer":"790/2",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"144/8",
			"answer":"144/8",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"747/3",
			"answer":"747/3",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"497/7",
			"answer":"497/7",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"428/4",
			"answer":"428/4",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"612/9",
			"answer":"612/9",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"675/9",
			"answer":"675/9",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"252/7",
			"answer":"252/7",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"973/7",
			"answer":"973/7",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},	
		
		{
			"Problem":"208/8",
			"answer":"208/8",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"126/6",
			"answer":"126/6",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"332/4",
			"answer":"332/4",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"480/2",
			"answer":"480/2",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"96/8",
			"answer":"96/8",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},	

		{
			"Problem":"265/5",
			"answer":"265/5",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"904/4",
			"answer":"904/4",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"368/8",
			"answer":"368/8",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"320/4",
			"answer":"320/4",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"524/4",
			"answer":"524/4",
			"status":"unsolved"
		}	
	]
}